Joseph Sciorra collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
- Series 1. Religious feasts and processions/Giglio Feast and other (primarily Italian American) religious feasts and processions, ca. 1903-2018
  - Joe Sciorra, Giglio, tape 1, June 1, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR001; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Joseph Sciorra Masters thesis on Giglio, 1987, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 7/4)
  - Joseph Sciorra paper for Charles Briggs-Molly Manna, 1989-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 7/5)
  - Joseph Iovino interview, 1981, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 7/6)
  - Joseph Iovino, tape 4, June 17, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR011; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Larry Lorenzano, September 25, 1984, AFC 2018/065: SR096; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Last meeting before feast of Giglio and distribution of letters and t-shirts. July 2, 1981, opening/Feast; July 9, 1981, children's Giglio. Tape 7, July 1-9, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR007; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Last meeting before feast of Giglio and distribution of letters and t-shirts. July 2, 1981, opening/Feast; July 9, 1981, children's Giglio. Tape 7, July 1-9, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR014; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Legend paper by Sciorra, 1989, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 7/7)
  - Lift Mass, Ikie Peluso, July 12, 1981. Tape 10, July 12, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR022; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Long Island Feast, 1999-2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 7/8)
  - Lou Nasti, February 24, 2006, AFC 2018/065: SR206; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Louise Petrosino; Amsterdam, New York, May 12, 1982, AFC 2018/065: SR201; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Memories of the Dancing Giglio, undated, AFC 2018/065: MV015; 1 videocassette
  - Mentoring Project for Folk Arts Programming, ca. 1991, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 7/9)
  - Metaphors of masculinity, 1986, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 7/10)
  - Mike and Louis Farinaccio interview, 1981, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 7/11)
  - Mike Camaro, November 18, 1982; Pete Donna, November 20, 1982. Tape 12, November 18-20, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR061; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Mike Camaro, November 18, 1982; Pete Donna, November 20, 1982. Tape 12, November 18-20, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR068; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Misc. Italian feasts and processions, 1988, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 7/12)
  - Molly Manna interview transcription, 1981, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 7/13)
  - Mr. and Mrs. Tom Bello and Nat Bello, tape 1C, May 10, 1983, AFC 2018/065: SR074; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Mr. and Mrs. Tom Bello and Nat Bello, tape 1C, May 10-14, 1983, AFC 2018/065: SR077; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Mr. and Mrs. Tom Bello and son, Nat Bello; Eddie Di Domenico, wife, daughter, and son, Anthony. Tape 2C, May 10-14, 1983, AFC 2018/065: SR076; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Mr. and Mrs. Tom Bello and son, Nat Bello; Mrs. and Mr. Eddie Di Domenico, daughter and her son, Anthony, May 10-14, 1983, AFC 2018/065: SR075; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Mr. Anthony Barricelli and Ida Cessa and Corinne (?); Earl Guirto (?) and Mrs. Guirto, October 5-21, 1983, AFC 2018/065: SR091; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Mr. Martello, tape 1, June 5, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR008; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Mr. Sam Cangiano. 6 year old kid singing Giglio song and commando. Tape 6, June 25, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR006; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Mrs. Molly Manna, her daughter, and Elizabeth Sperarge (?) and Margaret "Our Lady of Snow." Tape 14, July 22, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR029; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Mt. Carmel processions/shrines - Rosebank, Staten Island, ca. 1989, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 7/14)
  - Mt. Carmel Rosebank, Staten Island. Interview with visitors. Nancy Russo, July 14, 1991, AFC 2018/065: SR199; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Mt. Carmel Rosebank, William Durden, April 1, 1989, AFC 2018/065: SR197; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Music - Harlem/Bronx Feast, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 7/15)
  - Music - New Jersey Feast, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 7/16)
  - Music - Queens Feast, 2002, undated, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 7/17)
  - National Italian American Foundation (NIAF), Giglio book, 2003, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 7/18)
  - Neighborhoods Today, Giglio Sunday, 58 minutes, undated, AFC 2018/065: MV004; 1 videocassette
  - New Jersey Feast, 1983, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 7/19)
  - New Jersey Feast, 1983, AFC 2018/065: PH031; 17 slides, color (35mm) (Box 50)
  - New Jersey Giglio, 1983, AFC 2018/065: PH062; 3 slides, color (35mm) (Box 56)
  - New Jersey Giglio, December 11, 2003, AFC 2018/065: SR174; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - New Yorker article about Giglio, 1990, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 7/20)
  - Nola (Italy) - Brooklyn connection, 1974-2006, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 7/21)
  - Nola ephemera, ca. 1982-1987, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 7/22)
  - Nola feast memorabilia, ca. 1982-2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 8/1)
  - Nola feast: miscellaneous articles and stuff, 1979-1995, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 8/2)
  - Nola field notes and photographs, 1/2, ca. 1983-1986, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 8/3)
  - Nola field notes and photographs, 2/2, ca. 1983-1986, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 8/4)
  - Nola field notes and photographs, ca. 1983-1986, AFC 2018/065: PH002; 28 slides, color (35mm) (Box 47)
    Nola Festa Dei Gigli, June 1983.
  - Nola field notes and photographs, ca. 1983-1986, AFC 2018/065: PH087; 96 film negatives, black and white (35mm) (Box 61)
  - Nola newspapers, 1982-1986, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 45/1)
  - Nola talk, 1982-1985, 2005, 2005, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 45/4)
  - Nola talk, 1982-1985, 2005, 2005, AFC 2018/065: PH010; 24 slides, color (35mm) (Box 48)
  - Nola, tape 1. Maestro di festi dep pilio del Pouettiere (images in collection folder), June 28, 1983, AFC 2018/065: SR084; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Nola, tape 2. Gaetano de Gislameo, tape 2 (images in collection folder), June 28-29, 1983, AFC 2018/065: SR085; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Nola, tape 3 (images in collection folder), June 29, 1983, AFC 2018/065: SR086; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Nola, tape 4, July, 1983, AFC 2018/065: SR087; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Non-Italian processions, 1990-1994, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 8/5)
  - Non-Italian processions, 1990-1994, AFC 2018/065: PH088; 5 film negatives, color
  - Nunziata Brothers, 1991, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 8/6)
  - Nunziata Brothers Conselyea St. Giglio, 1990, AFC 2018/065: PH050; 27 slides, color (35mm) (Box 54)
    Photographs by Martha Cooper
  - Nunziata Brothers - measured drawings for frame, ca. 1991, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 8/7)
  - NYU Performance Studies Masters of Arts Thesis, 1983-1985, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 8/8)
  - NYU Performance Studies Masters of Arts Thesis - miscellaneous drafts, ca. 1983-1984, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 46/1)
  - O'Giglio e Paradiso article, 1986-1989, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 8/9)
  - OLMC, Harlem, 1/3, ca. 2004, 1 folder of manuscripts with 24 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 8/10)
  - OLMC, Harlem, 2/3, ca. 2004, 1 folder of manuscripts with 22 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 8/11)
  - OLMC, Harlem, 3/3, ca. 2004, 1 folder of manuscripts with 29 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 8/12)
  - OLMC, Harlem, ca. 2004, AFC 2018/065: PH101; 86 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 62)
  - OLMC Feast and Grotto literature, ca. 2009, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 8/13)
  - OLMC (Our Lady of Mount Carmel) Grotto, Staten Island, Rosebank, Mike De Cataldo, Themin Charelli (?), Dick Russo, tape 2; Louis Russo, March 6-18, 1989, AFC 2018/065: SR195; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - OLMC (Our Lady of Mount Carmel) Rosebank, Staten Island, July 16, 1989, AFC 2018/065: SR198; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - OLMC (Our Lady of Mount Carmel) Rosebank, Staten Island. Vito Russo, Thomas Charelli, Mike De Cataldo, tape 1, March 6, 1989, AFC 2018/065: SR194; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Our Lady, July 16, 1981; Children's Giglio and boat, July 17, 1981; Richard Oats, Morra, Peter Peluso. Tape 12, July 16-17, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR026; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Our Lady, Shrine ladies, July 16, 1981; Children's Giglio and boat, July 17, 1981; Interview with Richard "Oats," Morra (good recording), Peter Peluso. Tape 12, July 16-17, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR027; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Our Lady of Mercy procession, 1986-2008, 67 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 8/14)
  - Our Lady of Mercy procession, 1986-2008, AFC 2018/065: PH129; 60 film negatives, color (35mm); 27 film negatives, black and white (35mm) (Box 65)
  - Our Lady of Mount Carmel Church, ca. 1987-2014, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 8/15)
  - Our Lady of Mercy procession, April 27, 1986, AFC 2018/065: PH049; 19 slides, color (35mm) (Box 54)
  - Our Lady of Mount Carmel Society 100th Anniversary "Souvenir Journal," 2000, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 8/16)
  - Our Lady of the Snow, 1982, AFC 2018/065: PH044; 6 slides, color (35mm) (Box 53)
  - Our Lady of the Snow, 1/2, ca. 1982-2015, 1 folder of manuscripts with 7 photographic prints, color (3.5x5); 1 photographic print, black and white (1985 Good Friday procession); 1 contact sheet (8.5x11) (Box-folder 8/17)
  - Our Lady of the Snow, 1/2, ca. 1982-2015, AFC 2018/065: PH123; 11 film negatives, color (35mm); 37 film negatives, black and white (35mm) (Box 65)
  - Our Lady of the Snow, 2/2, ca. 1982-2015, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 9/1)
  - Our Lady of the Snow, outs, undated, AFC 2018/065: PH060; 42 slides, color (35mm) (Box 56)
    some or all photographs by Martha Cooper
  - Our Lady of the Snow and the St. Sabino procession, Williamsburg, Brooklyn, August 5, 1986, AFC 2018/065: PH045; 63 slides, color (35mm) (Box 53-54)
  - Paul Sheridan's photos, Brooklyn and Queens, 1987-1990, 1 folder of manuscripts with 14 photographic prints, black and white (11 are size 5x8; 3 are size 8x10) (Box-folder 9/2)
  - Peter Peluso interview, tape 2, 1981, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 9/3)
  - Peter Peluso interview, tape 3, 1981, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 9/4)
  - Peter Peluso, tape 2, June 10-16, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR002; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Peter Peluso, tape 2, June 10-16, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR009; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Peter Peluso, tape 3, June 16, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR003; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Peter Peluso, tape 3, June 16, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR010; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Phil and Joann Manna, tape 13, February 11, 1983, AFC 2018/065: SR062; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Phil and Joann Manna, tape 13, February 11, 1983, AFC 2018/065: SR073; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Phil and Joann Manna, tape 14, February 11, 1983, AFC 2018/065: SR063; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Phil and Joann Manna, tape 14, February 11, 1983, AFC 2018/065: SR103; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Phil Caccavalle, October 23, 1982, AFC 2018/065: SR058; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Phil Caccavalle interview, 1982, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 9/5)
  - Phil Caccavalle, tape 10, October 23, 1982, AFC 2018/065: SR066; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Processions: paper about hierarchy and conflict, 1986, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 9/6)
  - Processions: Station of Cross, OLMC (Our Lady of Mount Carmel); Settino and Theresa Corvino, April 5-10, 1985, AFC 2018/065: SR109; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Processional images (Poritello?), ca. 1985-1986, AFC 2018/065: PH073; 19 slides, color (35mm) (Box 59)
  - Queens Council on the Arts photo prints, ca. 1982-1987, 1 folder of manuscripts with 7 photographic prints, black and white (8x10) (Box-folder 9/7)
  - Queens Council on the Arts photo prints, ca. 1982-1987, AFC 2018/065: PH006; 1 slide, black and white (Box 47)
  - Queens project/Giglio, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR127; 1 sound tape reel: 7 in., analog
  - Questua, July 10; Big lift, July 11; Children's boat and Giglio, July 13, July 10-13, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR041; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Questua, July 10; Big lift, July 11; Children's boat and Giglio, July 13 (Tape 1), July 10-13, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR042; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Questua, July 11; End Giglio/boat, July 12, July 11-12, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR019; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Questua, July 11; Giglio and boat, July 12, July 11-12, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR018; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Questua, July 11; Mass, July 12. Tape 9, July 11-12, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR016; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Questua, July 11; N. Ambrosino (butcher), Lune of Mass, July 12. Tape 9, July 11-12, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR020; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Raffaela Petarza; Severna Coscia, July, 2005, AFC 2018/065: SR205; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Review of Giglio documentary, 2004-2005, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 9/8)
  - Romualdo Martello, ca. 1981-1982, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 9/9)
  - Romualdo Martello interview, 1981, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 9/10)
  - Saint Fortunata procession, Bensonhurst, Brooklyn, 1985-2013, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 9/11)
  - Saint Fortunata procession, Bensonhurst, Brooklyn, 1985, AFC 2018/065: PH039; 33 slides, color (35mm) (Box 53)
  - Sal and Carmela (?) and daughter Angela, September 17, 1984, AFC 2018/065: SR095; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Sam Cangiano interview, tape 5, 1981, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 9/12)
  - Sam Cangiano interview, tape 6, 1981, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 9/13)
  - Sam Cangiano. 6 year old kid singing Giglio song and commando. Tape 6, June 25, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR013; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Sam Iovino (2). Tape 8, September 4, 1982, AFC 2018/065: SR065; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Sam Iovino (3) (tape 9); Phil Caccavalle (1), September 4-October 23, 1982, AFC 2018/065: SR059; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Sam Iovino and wife, interview with Joe and Shelley Posen. Tape 7, September 4, 1982, AFC 2018/065: SR054; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Sam Iovino interview, 1982, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 9/14)
  - Sam Iovino, P, JS. Tape 7, September 4, 1982, AFC 2018/065: SR055; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Sam Iovino (tape 3); Phil Caccavalle, September 4-October 23, 1982, AFC 2018/065: SR057; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Sam Iovino. Tape 2, September 4, 1982, AFC 2018/065: SR056; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Sarge Merando. Tape 17, August 3, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR035; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Sarge Merando, part 2. Tape 17, August 3, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR034; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Sarge Mirando and Mike Camaro, tape 11, November 18, 1982, AFC 2018/065: SR060; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Sarge Mirando and Mike Camaro, tape 11, 1982, AFC 2018/065: SR102; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Sarge Mirando interview, 1981, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 9/15)
  - Sarge, Buster, Sam Iovino, Bosti, Sammy, Joe Peluso, Jimmie Smith at Sarge's; Sarge's house, preline of March, July 18, 1982, AFC 2018/065: SR048; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Sarge's house, Sammy Iovino, Buster, Sarge, Sammy/Joe Peluso/Jimmie Smith (Tape 3), July 18, 1982, AFC 2018/065: SR046; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Shelley (Posen)'s writing, Giglio, 1981, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 9/16)
  - Shrine Church of Our Lady of Mount Carmel, 100th Anniversary (book), 1987, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 9/17)
  - Side A: Archibald "Iky" Peluso. Side B: July 16, 1981, July 12-16, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR024; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Side A: Day of the bag lift, 1. Game of moro, July 12; Our Lady: Mrs. Peluso shrines, July 16. Side B: Shrines, Mrs. Peluso, July 16, July 12-16, 1981, AFC 2018/065: SR025; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Smithsonian Institution Human Studies FIlm Archives "Brooklyn Giglio, 1956," tape 4, March 25, 1985, AFC 2018/065: MV007; 1 videocassette
  - Smithsonian Institution Human Studies FIlm Archives "Brooklyn San Paola Festival, 1950," tape 3, March 25, 1985, AFC 2018/065: MV006; 1 videocassette
  - Smithsonian Institution Human Studies FIlm Archives "Brooklyn San Paulino Feast ca. 1939," tape 2, March 25, 1985, AFC 2018/065: MV005; 1 videocassette
  - St. Anthony Feast, Williamsburg, 1993-2006, 1 folder of manuscripts with 6 photographic prints, color (4x6) (Box-folder 9/18)
  - St. Anthony Feast, Williamsburg, 1993-2006, AFC 2018/065: PH124; 12 film negatives, color (35mm) (Box 65)
  - St. Cono procession, Williamsburg, Brooklyn, 1983-1986, AFC 2018/065: PH047; 25 slides, color (35mm) (Box 54)
  - St. Cono procession, Williamsburg, Brooklyn, 1/2, 1984-2008, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 9/19)
  - St. Cono procession, Williamsburg, Brooklyn, 2/2, 1984-2008, 1 folder of manuscripts with 13 photographic prints (8 are 4x6 color, 4 are 5x6 color, 1 is 5x7 black and white), 1 contact sheet (Box-folder 9/20)
  - St. Cono procession, Williamsburg, Brooklyn, 2/2, 1984-2008, AFC 2018/065: PH127; 19 film negatives, color (35mm); 35 film negatives, black and white (35mm) (Box 65)
  - St. Nick's All Soul's Day Parade, 1994, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 9/21)
  - St. Padre Pio (religious banner form), 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 9/22)
  - St. Padre Pio Society, 2007, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 9/23)
  - St. Paulinus of Nola Feast, dissertation attempt, 1988-1992, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 10/1)
  - St. Paulinus of Nola Feast, dissertation proposal, 1988-1992, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 10/2)
  - St. Sabino banner/procession, 1984-2013, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 10/3)
  - The Men Who Dance the Giglio, a film by Jeff Porter. 28 minutes, undated, AFC 2018/065: MV001; 1 videocassette
  - Tuddy Ferrara. Tape 4C, May 27, 1983, AFC 2018/065: SR080; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Tuddy Ferrara. Tape 4C (inaudible), May 27, 1983, AFC 2018/065: SR081; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Tuddy Ferrara; Roberto Murolo, 1981-1985, AFC 2018/065: SR107; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Turk Night (Feast), 1994-2001, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 10/4)
  - Vivona, undated, AFC 2018/065: SR070; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Vivona, undated, AFC 2018/065: SR071; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - Watching Giglio slides OLMC (Our Lady of Mount Carmel), 1981-1985, AFC 2018/065: SR114; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - WBAI - Greenpoint-Williamsburg, March 30, 1984, AFC 2018/065: SR094; 1 sound cassette: analog
  - "We Go Where the Italians Live" (article), 1992-1993, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 10/5)
  - "We Go Where the Italians Live" (article), final paper, 1996, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 10/6)
  - Yearbook I Gigli Di Nola, 1982, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 10/7)
  - Yearbook I Gigli Di Nola, 1983, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 10/8)
  - Yearbook I Gigli Di Nola, 1984, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 10/9)
  - Yearbook I Gigli Di Nola, 1985, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 10/10)
  - Yearbook I Gigli Di Nola, 1986, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 10/11)
  - Yearbook I Gigli Di Nola, 2002, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 10/12)
  - Our Lady of Mount Carmel (OLMC) Church - Brooklyn Eagle research, 2003-2005, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 10/13)
  - Our Lady of Mount Carmel (OLMC) Church bulletin, 1983-2018, 1 folder of manuscripts (Box-folder 11/1)
  - Our Lady of Mt. Carmel Fraternal Society, 1986-2003, 1 folder of manuscripts with 2 photographic prints, color (4x6), 1 contact sheet (Box-folder 11/2)
  - Our Lady of Mt. Carmel Fraternal Society, 1986-2003, AFC 2018/065: PH128; 36 film negatives, black and white (35mm) (Box 65)
  - Subseries 1. Oversized materials related to Giglio feast and associated events, ca. 1984-2018
    - Annual Feast: Giglio di Sant' Antonio of East Harlem, August 9-12, 2018, AFC 2018/065: GR001; 1 poster (Folder OS01)
    - Sketch of festival layout (on graph paper), undated, AFC 2018/065: GR002; 1 piece of graph paper (Folder OS01)
    - Astoria's 2nd Annual Feast, Giglio di San Paolino, June 22-25, 1989, AFC 2018/065: GR003; 1 poster (Folder OS01)
    - 8th Annual Feast, Giglio di San Antonio, August 3-13, 1989, AFC 2018/065: GR004; 1 poster (Folder OS01)
    - Our Lady of Mount Carmel Feast (Giglio Society of East Harlem), 121st Anniversary, July 14-24, 2005, AFC 2018/065: GR005; 1 poster (Folder OS02)
    - Feast 2005, 118th Annual Our Lady of Mount Carmel Feast and Bazaar (Williamsburg), July 7-17, 2005, AFC 2018/065: GR006; 1 poster (Folder OS02)
    - 105th Annual Our Lady of Mt. Carmel Church and St. Paulinus Feast & Bazaar (Williamsburg), July 2-16, 1992, AFC 2018/065: GR007; 1 poster (Folder OS02)
    - Mt. Carmel Feast & Bazaar, July 7 to 18 (106th Annual), July 7-18 (no year), AFC 2018/065: GR008; 1 poster (Folder OS02)
    - Mt. Carmel Feast & Bazaar, July 7 to 18 (106th Annual), July 7-18 (no year), AFC 2018/065: GR009; 1 poster (Folder OS02)
    - Coors Our Lady of Mt. Carmel Shrine Church 103rd Annual Feast & Bazaar, July 5-16, 1990, AFC 2018/065: GR010; 1 poster (Folder OS02)
    - Feast of Our Lady of Mt. Carmel & St. Paulinus (Brooklyn), July 2-19 (no year), AFC 2018/065: GR011; 1 poster (Folder OS03)
    - 84th Annual Feast, Our Lady of Mount Carmel Society (Rosebank, Staten Island), July 10-19 (no year), AFC 2018/065: GR012; 1 poster (Folder OS03)
    - 85th Annual Feast, Our Lady of Mount Carmel Society (Rosebank, Staten Island), July 8-17 (no year), AFC 2018/065: GR013; 1 poster (Folder OS03)
    - 88th Annual Feast, Our Lady of Mount Carmel Society (Rosebank, Staten Island), July 5-16 (no year), AFC 2018/065: GR014; 1 poster (Folder OS03)
    - Feast of the Healing Saints, 79th Annual, Saints Cosmas & Damian (Cambridge, Massachusetts), September 10-11, 2005, AFC 2018/065: GR015; 1 poster (Folder OS03)
    - Budweiser 96th Annual Feast of the Shrine of Our Lady of Mt. Carmel, June 28-July 16, 1984, AFC 2018/065: GR016; 1 poster (Folder OS03)
    - Sketch map of Our Lady of Mount Carmel Grotto, Staten Island, NY, undated, AFC 2018/065: GR017; 1 print of an ink drawing (Folder OS04)
    - Our Lady of Mount Carmel Feast, 120th Anniversary, New York, NY, July 8-18, 2004, AFC 2018/065: GR018; 1 poster (Folder OS04)
    - Nunziata Bros. Presents the 1st Annual Dancing of the Giglio (Brooklyn), July 29, 1990, AFC 2018/065: GR019; 1 poster (Folder OS04)
    - The 2nd Annual Dancing of the Giglio featuring Tuddy Ferrara (Brooklyn), July 28, 1991, AFC 2018/065: GR020; 1 poster (Folder OS04)
    - Italian Evening Bulletin (newspaper), 1910, AFC 2018/065: GR021; 1 photo print of newspaper (Folder OS04)
    - 101st Anniversary Feast, Our Lady of Mount Carmel Society (Rosebank, Staten Island), July 8-18, 2004, AFC 2018/065: GR022; 1 poster (Folder OS04)
    - 106th Anniversary Feast, Our Lady of Mount Carmel Society (Rosebank, Staten Island), July 9-19, 2009, AFC 2018/065: GR023; 1 poster (Folder OS04)
    - 106th Anniversary Feast, Our Lady of Mount Carmel Society (Rosebank, Staten Island), July 9-19, 2009, AFC 2018/065: GR024; 1 poster (Folder OS04)
    - OLMC Feast 2017 in Honor of Our Lady of Mount Carmel & San Paolino di Nola, July 5-16, 2017, AFC 2018/065: GR025; 1 poster (Folder OS04)
    - 2018 OLMC Feast in Honor of Our Lady of Mount Carmel and San Paolino di Nola, July 5-16, 2018, AFC 2018/065: GR026; 1 poster (Folder OS04)
    - 2018 OLMC Feast in Honor of Our Lady of Mount Carmel and San Paolino di Nola, July 5-16, 2018, AFC 2018/065: GR027; 1 poster (Folder OS04)
    - 2013 OLMC Feast in Honor of Our Lady of Mount Carmel and San Paolino di Nola, July 10-21, 2013, AFC 2018/065: GR028; 1 poster (Folder OS04)
    - 2013 OLMC Feast in Honor of Our Lady of Mount Carmel and San Paolino di Nola, July 10-21, 2013, AFC 2018/065: GR029; 1 poster (Folder OS04)